Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Keith Stewart Thomson as dean, 1979-1986; Accession 2004-A-143
  - Memoranda
    - Policies and Procedures Governing the Appointment of Graduate Students to Teach in Yale College and the Graduate School, 1971 October 25 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Nondiscrimination…, 1971 October 15 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Senate Bill 659, 1971 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - 1971 Sep 27 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - The Effect of Federal Actions and Proposed Actions Upon the Graduate School (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - 1971 Aug 24 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - 1971 Aug 13 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - 1971 Aug 12 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - 1971 Aug 11 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - 1971 Aug 10 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Sources of Income Providing Financial Aid for Graduate Students (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - Recommendations of the Executive Committee Concerning Final Report of Governance (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - 1971 May 7 (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - 1971 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - to DGS, 1971 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - to Students, 1971 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - Joint Procedures on Appointments, 1971 April 28 (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - Possible Abolition of NDEA Fellowships, 1971 April 22 (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - Financial Aid to Students…, 1971 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - 1971 Feb 22 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - 1971 Feb 4 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Requests for Comments, 1971 January 21 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - Admissions for Financial Aid, 1971 January 15 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - 1971 Jan 3 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - 1970 Aug 21 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - 1970 May 11 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - 1970 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - 1970 May 5 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - 1970 Apr 26 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - Summer Fellowships, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - Financial Aid to Students Admitted 1970-1971, 1970 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Admission and Financial Aid 1970-1971, 1970 January 20 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - B.A./M.A. Joint Degrees, 1970 January 6 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Memoranda to DGS, 1969 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Deficit in 1969-1970 Fellowship Budget, 1969 September 8 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Action of the Faculty of the Graduate School Concerning the Establishment of a Committee in Discipline, 1969 June 6 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Demand for Ph.D.'s; Graduate Finance Crisis; University Must Protect Self; etc. (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Yale-Princeton Proposal (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Memorandum of, 1975 January 27 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Meeting of the Dwarfs, 1973 November 17 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - A Student's Guide to the Yale Health Plan (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Yale Health Plan Supplemental Major Medical (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Photographs - FAS Faculty (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - High Lights - A Handbook for the Yale Staff (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Alumni Fund (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Alumni Fund Letters, Fall 1983 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Alumni Fund (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Challenge Fund Letters (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Alumni Fund (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Dean Darlington (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - ACE Survey, 1973 April (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - ACE (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Aptheker (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Archival Records (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Association of American Universities (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - AYA (Box 7, Folder 215 - 216)
  - Bursar's Office (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Center for the Study of Southern Culture (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Career Advisory and Planning Office (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Committee on Expository Writing (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Danforth Fellowships (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Dwarfs Meeting, 1975 October 4 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Dwarfs (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Dwarfs Meeting, 1981 May 8 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Dwarfs (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Augmented Dwarfs (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Faculty Research Grants, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Committee on Faculty Research Grants (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Committee on Faculty Research Grants, May 11, 3:00 pm (Box 8, Folder 230)
  - Research Development Committee (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Committee on Retirement (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Committee on the Freedom of Expression at Yale (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - University Council Committee on the Graduate School (Box 8, Folder 235)
  - Commencement, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 236 - 241)
  - Wilbur Cross
    - Nominations, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Nominations, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - Wilbur L. Cross Medal Nominees, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    - Nominations, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 245)
    - Nominations, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 246)
    - Medal Citations, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 247)
    - Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 248)
    - Medal Citations, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - Citations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 250)
    - Nominations, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 251)
    - Medal, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 252)
    - Nominations, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 253)
    - Medal Nominees, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Draft (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Dwarfs (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Effort Reporting (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Graduate Educations National Problems (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Senate (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Training in the Health Services (Box 9, Folder 260)
  - Higher Education Research Institute (Box 9, Folder 261)
  - Institutional Relations and Alumni Programs (Box 9, Folder 262)
  - Meeting - Charles Lord, 1977 July 13 (Box 9, Folder 263)
  - Leonine Commission (Box 9, Folder 264)
  - Kernan (Box 9, Folder 265)
  - Nominations for Fellowships to Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 9, Folder 266)
  - Paul Kanzer Graduate Fellowships 589A-1931-1932395 (Box 9, Folder 269)
  - Edgar S. Furniss (Box 9, Folder 272)
  - Prize Teaching Fellow Meeting - 414 SSS, 1981 May 11 (Box 9, Folder 273)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Committee on Athletics (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Senate (Box 9, Folder 279)
  - Manfile (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Media Design Studio (Box 9, Folder 281)
  - Murphy Professorships (Box 9, Folder 282)
  - National Foundation for Cancer Research (Box 9, Folder 283)
  - National Commission on Research (Box 9, Folder 284)
  - Patents (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Pavlavi University (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Peabody Museum Search Committee (Box 9, Folder 287)
  - Peabody Museum Search (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Letters re: Peabody Search (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Peabody Museum Search (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Bureau of Purchases (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Retirements
    - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 294)
    - 1983 (Box 9, Folder 295)
    - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 296)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 297)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 298)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 299)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Retirements (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Numbering of Courses (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Sherry H. Penney - Associate Provost (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Pell - Green Bill (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Study Group on Yale College (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Authors for Ventures (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - Physics and Society (Box 10, Folder 308)
  - Ventures (Box 10, Folder 309)
  - Office of Education (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Chairmen of Councils (Box 10, Folder 311)
  - Faculty Research Grants, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Committee on Faculty Research Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Yale Center (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - Yale College (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Administrative Sciences (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - African Studies (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - American Studies (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Biology (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Faculty Research Grant Committee (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Chairmen of Councils (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Concilium (Box 10, Folder 322 - 324)
  - Council of Engineering (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Economics (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - English (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Forestry (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - French (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Discussion with George Veronis - 2:00 p.m., 1977 November 4 (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - Geology and Geophysics (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - History (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - History of Science (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Organization and Management (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Organization and Management - Pelikan (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Political Science (Box 11, Folder 338 - 339)
  - Psychology (Box 11, Folder 340 - 341)
  - Judaic Studies (Box 11, Folder 342)
  - Religious Studies (Box 11, Folder 343)
  - Sociology (Box 11, Folder 345)
- Records of John Perry Miller as dean, 1961-1969; Accession 2004-A-150
  - Budget - Graduate School, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Alumni Fund - 8700-35-66402, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - B.A.-M.A. Degree, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School Association Fund - 8700-35-66400, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Permanent Officers - Graduate School, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University Council Committee on the Graduate School, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Student Housing, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee on International Studies - Organization Reports, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on International Relations, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs Finding Committee, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - International Studies - Current, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Relations, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - M.A.T., 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - M.A.T. Annual Reports, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching
    - 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1939-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - John Hay Fellows Program (MAT), 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - MAT - Science Promam, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - MAT - History Program, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - MAT Committee on Training Secondary School Teachers, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Qualifications for Advanced Standing, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Advances and Temporary Loans, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Riot Provision - Education Legislation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Application Fee - Graduate School, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Assessment of Quality in Graduate Education, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Assistantship Data, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - B.A.-M.A. Degree Inquiries (General Correspondence), 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Central Clearance Use University Facilities, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Class and Examination Schedules, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Coalition for a New University, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - College Fellows Affiliation, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - College Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Convocation - Incoming Students Material JPM, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cost of Education Allowance - Federal Fellowships and Traineeships, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Departmental Codes - IBM, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Discipline Report - President's Committee, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dissertation Readers - Outside, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dissertation Fee - Proration 1969, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Dissertation Information - Library, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dissertation Information - General, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Microfilming Dissertations, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - ETS Language Exam Scores - Departmental, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Requests for Evaluation of Students, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Faculty and Non-faculty Scholarship Plan, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fellowship and Traineeship Stipends, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Five-Year B.A. Experiment, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Foreign Language Requirements, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Foreign Language Testing Data, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - General Appropriation - Fellowships Request, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - General Appropriations Request - Graduate School Fellowships, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Grades - Graduate Students, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Grading, Quality Requirement, Extensions, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Graduate Affiliates, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Graduate Affiliates, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Yale Graduate Professional Publication, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Graduate Record Examination Score Interpretation, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Graduate School Growth, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Graduate School House Committee File 2, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Graduate Student Discipline Cases, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Graduate Student Full-Time Appointments to Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Graduate Student Council, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Graduate Student Housing JPM - Questionnaire and Article, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Graduate Student Housing Rent Adjustments, 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Graduate Student Teaching - Yale College and Graduate School, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Housing Committee - ERW, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - "Hall" Report, 1968 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Housing - Visiting Faculty, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Integration - HGS and HHH, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Intermediate Deaee - JPM Article, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Junior Fellows, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Language - Requirements in the Sciences, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Language Requirements - Social Sciences, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Language Requirement, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Language Tests, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Language Tests - Foreign Students, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Master's Degree Language Requirements, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Language Requirements - Ph.D. Degree, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Language Reading Courses, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Language Substitution, 1963 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Committee on Language Teaching, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Loans - Miscellaneous Information, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Master's Degree Requirements- Entering Students, Fall, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Terminal M.A. Programs to be Discussed with Graduate School Executive Committee, 1966 October (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - M.A.-LLB Joint Program Procedures, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - M.D.-Ph.D. Joint Program, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Master of Science Degree in Engineering - Part-Time Basis, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Negros, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Numbering System of Courses, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Occupational Deferment - Graduate Students, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Proration of Dissertation Fee, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Proration of Tuition Due to Draft, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Readmission After Military Service, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Riots, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Revenues and Expenditures - Graduate School Exclusive of Fellowships, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Room Rental Charges, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Seminars - Governing of the University, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Statistics, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Statistics - Other Universities, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Student Affairs - Graduate School, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Student Activism, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Student Protests, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Student Record Keeping Procedures, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Summer Programs, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Student Suggestions, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Teaching Assistants - General, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Teaching Interns - Others Schools, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Committee on Teaching of Science, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Teaching Interns, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Terminal Date Extensions, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Transfer Requests, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Tuition Rates, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Tuition - Accounting Instructions, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - University College - JPM, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Work-Study Program - Summer, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Computer Science Program, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Dean Taylor, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Concilium, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Furniture and Equipment Requests, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Officers of the Graduate Student Senate, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Graduate Student Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Meetings of the Senate, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Graduate Student Senate, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - HGS, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - HGS Security, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Proposals for Capital Improvements, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - University Committee on Summer Programs, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - MAT Budget, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - MAT, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - MAT Program, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Intensive Summer Studies Program, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - HGS Office Lists, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Graduate Student Senate, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Leave of Absence Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - HGS Tower Rentals, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Ford Proposal - Work Sheets, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Graduate School Pumoses, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Alumni Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Commencement Information June, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Graduate School Committee Lists, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Graduate School Committee Correspondence - DGS Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Biological Sciences Department Actions - Panning and Review, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Biological Sciences Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Biological Sciences - Committee on Degrees, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Degree Committees, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Graduate School Tuition Estimates (For Treasurer), 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Joint Board Agenda Lists, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Joint Boards of Permanent Officers List Appointments Fall, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Senior Appointments Material, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Administrative Sciences, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - American Studies, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Anthropology, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Astronomy, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Astronomy, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Anthropology, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Biology, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Biometry, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Biochemistry, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Biophysics, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Botany, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Chemistry, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Chemistry, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Classics, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Comparative Literature, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Conservation, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Economics, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Economics, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Education, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - English, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Engineering, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - French, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Geochronometric Laboratory, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Geography, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Geology, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Geology, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - History, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - History, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - History of Art, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - History of Music, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - History of Science and Medicine, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Indic and Far Eastern Languages, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - International Relations, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Italian, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Linguistics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Mathematics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Mathematics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Mathematics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Microbiology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Molecular Biology and Biophysics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Molecular Biophysics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Near Eastern Languages, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Philosophy, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Physics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Physics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Psychology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Political Science, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Psychology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Russian Studies, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Sociology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Sociology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Spanish, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Statistics, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Zoology, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Commencement - General Information, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Dean's Seminars, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Dissertation Ratings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Economic Opportunity Act, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Federal Income Tax - Graduate and Professional School Students, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Freshmen Counsellorships, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Graduate Affiliates, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Graduate Student Housing Survey, 1968 April 15 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Graduate Student Withdrawals List, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Offers of Financial Aid to incoming Students - Notice, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Policy Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - President's Committee on Discipline Report - September, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Research on Graduate Students, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Seesel and Anonymous Fellowships Committee on Post-Doctorates - Biological Sciences, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Sterling Fellowships Information, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Summer Activities, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Teaching Internships Proposal, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 236)
- Administrative records concerning finances of the Graduate School, maintained by Dean Donald W. Taylor, 1969-1975; Accession 2004-A-151
  - Budget - Graduate School, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Alumni Fund - 8700-1935-1966402, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - B.A.-M.A. Degree (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School Association Fund - 8700-1935-1966400 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Permanent Officers - Graduate School, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University Council Committee on the Graduate School, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Student Housing (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee on International Studies - Organization Reports (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on International Relations (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs Finding Committee (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - International Studies - Current (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Relations (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - M.A.T. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - M.A.T. Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching
    - 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)